Register of the Finnish Relief Fund records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Contributions File, 1939-1940
  - United States
    - New York
      - Cities/Burroughs/Counties
        - Long Island
          - Forest Hills (Folder 7)
          - Garden City (Folder 8)
          - Glen Head (Folder 9)
          - Great Neck (Folder 10)
          - Hampstead (Folder 11)
          - Hollis (Folder 12)
          - Huntington (Folder 13)
          - Jackson Heigts (Folder 14)
          - Jamaica (Folder 15)
          - Long Island City (Folder 16)
          - Manhasset (Folder 17)
          - Port Washington (Folder 18)
          - Richmond Hill (Box 156, Folder 1)
          - Syosset (Folder 2)
          - Woodhaven (Folder 3)
        - Mount Vernon (Folder 4)
        - New Rochelle (Folder 5)
        - New York City
          - General
            - Anonymous (Folder 6)
            - Finnish-American Relief Committee (Folder 7)
          - Brooklyn (Folder 8)
        - Newburgh (Folder 9)
        - Pelham (Folder 10)
        - Poughkeepsie (Folder 11)
        - Rye (Folder 12)
        - Scarsdale (Folder 13)
        - Schenectady (Box 157, Folder 1)
        - Staten Island (Folder 2)
        - Westchester County (Folder 3)
        - White Plains (Folder 4)
        - Yonkers (Folder 5)
      - Individuals
        - General (Folder 6-8)
        - General (Box 158, Folder 1-4)
        - Brooklyn (Folder 5-6)
        - Brooklyn (Box 159, Folder 1-6)
        - Long Island (Folder 7)
        - Long Island (Box 160, Folder 1-3)
        - New York City (Folder 4-8)
        - New York City (Box 161-168)
      - State organization (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - North Carolina
      - General (Folder 2)
      - State organization (Folder 3)
    - North Dakota
      - General (Folder 4)
      - State organization (Folder 5)
    - Ohio
      - Anonymous (Folder 6)
      - Cities
        - Canton (Folder 7)
        - Cincinnati (Folder 8)
        - Cleveland (Folder 9)
        - Columbus (Folder 10)
        - Toledo (Folder 11)
      - Individuals (Box 170, Folder 1-2)
      - State organization (Folder 3)
    - Oklahoma
      - General (Folder 4)
      - State organization (Folder 5)
    - Oregon
      - General (Folder 6)
      - State chairman (Folder 7-8)
      - State chairman (Box 171, Folder 1)
      - State organization (Folder 2-4)
    - Pennsylvania
      - Anonymous (Folder 5)
      - Cities
        - Lancaster (Folder 6)
        - Pittsburgh (Folder 7)
      - Individuals
        - General (Folder 8)
        - General (Box 172, Folder 1-5)
        - Philadelphia (Folder 6-7)
        - Philadelphia (Box 173, Folder 1)
      - State organization (Folder 2)
    - Rhode Island
      - General (Folder 3)
      - State organization (Folder 4)
    - South Carolina
      - General (Folder 5)
      - State organization (Folder 6)
    - South Dakota
      - General (Folder 7)
      - State organization (Folder 8)
    - Tennessee (Folder 9)
    - Texas
      - General (Folder 10)
      - State organization (Folder 11)
    - Utah (Box 174)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - State organization (Folder 2)
    - Vermont
      - General (Folder 3)
      - State organization (Folder 4)
    - Virginia
      - General (Folder 5)
      - Anonymous (Folder 6)
      - State organization (Folder 7)
    - Washington
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Anonymous (Folder 9)
      - Cities - Seattle (Folder 10)
      - State organization (Folder 11)
    - West Virginia
      - General (Folder 12)
      - State organization (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Wisconsin
      - General (Folder 2)
      - State organization (Folder 3)
    - Wyoming
      - General (Folder 4)
      - State organization (Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 6)
- Mayor's Committee File, 1939-1940
  Accounts, advertisements, insurance records, letters, postal issues, press releases, receipts, reports, tax records, telegrams, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - Advertisements - Department stores (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Acknowledgments (Folder 3)
      - Form letters (Folder 4)
      - Incoming letters (Folder 5)
      - Letters re export and import matters (Folder 6)
      - Refusals (Folder 7)
      - Request letters (Box 177, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder 2)
    - FRF divisions
      - Alcoholic Beverage (Folder 3)
      - American-Scandinavian
        - General (Folder 4)
        - Special Lecture Bureau (Folder 5)
      - Fannie Hurst's Writer (Folder 6)
      - Helen Hayes Stage (Folder 7)
      - Industrial (Folder 8)
  - Financial records
    - Accounts
      - General (Folder 9)
      - Guaranty Trust Co. (Folder 10)
      - Irving Trust Co.
        - General (Folder 11)
        - Special events account (Folder 12)
    - Receipts (Folder 13)
    - Receipts (Box 178, Folder 1-2)
  - Fundraising file
    - General
      - Book sales
        - General (Folder 3)
        - Air Babies (Folder 4)
        - International Year Book (Folder 5-6)
      - Stamp sales (Folder 7)
      - Tickets sales (Folder 8)
    - Committees
      - General
        - Arts (Folder 9)
        - Banks and Bankers (Folder 10)
        - Life Insurance (Folder 11)
        - Marine (Folder 12)
        - National Labor (Folder 13)
        - New York Stock Exchange (Folder 14)
        - Program (Folder 15)
        - Produce Exchange (Folder 16)
        - Women's Fashion (Folder 17)
      - New York City (Box 179)
        - Bronx (Folder 1)
        - Brooklyn (Folder 2)
        - Richmond (Folder 3)
        - Suffolk (Folder 4)
        - Queens (Folder 5)
        - Westchester (Folder 6)
    - Performers
      - Actors (Folder 7)
      - Musicians (singers, violinists, pianists) (Folder 8)
    - Special events
      - General. Includes program of events (Folder 9)
      - Auction - Knoedler Galleries (Folder 10)
      - Concerts
        - General, including at New Rochelle, New York (Folder 11)
        - Carnegie Hall, New York City (Folder 12)
        - Yale Glee Club, New York City (Folder 13)
      - Cruise (Folder 14)
      - Dance (Folder 15)
      - Finnish Cabaret (Folder 16)
      - Finnish Fair (Hotel Roosevelt) (Folder 17)
      - Games (Folder 18)
      - Ice Carnival (Folder 19)
      - Lectures (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Motion pictures
        - General (Folder 2)
        - Katia (Folder 3)
        - Soldiers Bride (Folder 4)
      - Parties (Folder 5)
      - Performances (Folder 6)
      - Shows
        - Antique (Folder 7)
        - Horse (Folder 8-9)
        - National Sportsmen's (Folder 10)
      - Songs (Folder 11)
    - Support groups
      - Carpenter's Union (Folder 12)
      - Clubs
        - General (Folder 13)
        - Danish Athletic (Folder 14)
        - Women's (Folder 15)
        - Yacht (Folder 16)
      - Colleges and schools (Folder 17)
      - Hotel Association of New York City
        - General (Folder 18)
        - Hotel Project (Folder 19)
      - Tolstoy Foundation (Box 181, Folder 1)
      - United Swedish Societies (Folder 2)
    - Volunteers
      - Collection work (Folder 3)
      - Office help (Folder 4)
      - Service (Folder 5-6)
  - Insurance records (Folder 7)
  - Postal issues (Folder 8)
  - Press releases (Folder 9)
  - Reports (Folder 10)
  - Tax records (Folder 11)
  - Telegrams (Folder 12)
- Subject File, 1939-1945
  Includes correspondence, historical material, maps, publications, programs, records of contributions, memoranda and reports arranged alphabetically by subject
  - Baking (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Boots and shoes (Folder 2)
  - Chemicals (Folder 3)
  - Churches (Folder 4)
  - Civilian Relief for Finland (Folder 5)
  - Clothing (Folder 6-9)
  - Committee in Brussels for Aid of Finland (Folder 10)
  - Croups (Folder 11)
  - Drive Aid to Finland. Mostly appeals to colleges and universities
    - General
      - Correspondence with National Collegiate Committee (Folder 12)
      - Summary of results (Folder 13)
    - Alabama-Arizona (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - California (Folder 2)
    - Colorado (Folder 3)
    - Connecticut (Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia (Folder 5)
    - Florida (Folder 6)
    - Georgia (Folder 7)
    - Illinois (Folder 8)
    - Indiana-Iowa (Folder 9)
    - Kansas (Folder 10)
    - Kentucky (Folder 11)
    - Louisiana (Folder 12)
    - Maine (Folder 13)
    - Maryland (Folder 14)
    - Massachusetts (Folder 15)
    - Michigan (Folder 16)
    - Minnesota-Mississippi (Folder 17)
    - Missouri (Folder 18)
    - Montana (Folder 19)
    - Nebraska-New Hampshire (Folder 20)
    - New Jersey (Folder 21)
    - New Mexico (Folder 22)
    - New York (Folder 23)
    - North Carolina (Folder 24)
    - North Dakota (Folder 25)
    - Ohio (Folder 26)
    - Oklahoma (Folder 27)
    - Oregon (Folder 28)
    - Pennsylvania (Folder 29)
    - Rhode Island (Folder 30)
    - South Carolina (Folder 31)
    - Tennessee (Folder 32)
    - Texas (Folder 33)
    - Utah (Folder 34)
    - Vermont (Folder 35)
    - Virginia (Folder 36)
    - Washington (Folder 37)
    - West Virginia (Folder 38)
    - Wisconsin (Folder 39)
    - Wyoming (Folder 40)
  - Fellowship for Finns (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Finland
    - General (Folder 2)
    - Decorations for people helping Finland
      - General (Folder 3)
      - Acceptances, refusals (Folder 4-5)
    - History - Revolution, 1917-1918. Fisher, Harold H., History of Finnish Independence, Typescript, 1941 (Folder 6)
    - Maps (Box 185)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - 1939-1940 (Folder 2)
      - 1940-1943 (Folder 3)
    - Opinions against and for relief
      - Criticism (Folder 4)
      - Debates (Folder 5)
    - Publications
      - Thirty Years of Anti-Tuberculosis Work in Finland, Helsinki, 1937 (Folder 6)
      - Kertomus, Toiminnasta, 1939 (Folder 7)
      - Relief Measures for the Part of the Population Suffering on Account of the War, Helsinki, 1940 (Folder 8)
      - The Finnish Relief Fund during the War Between Finland and the Soviet Union and Afterwards, Helsinki, 1940 (Folder 9)
      - The Finnish Relief Fund and the Provincial Centers of Voluntary Relief Work. Conference in Helsinki, 1940 February 21 (Folder 10)
      - The Finnish Relief Fund and the Provincial Centers of Voluntary Relief Work. Second meeting of representatives in Helsinki, 1940 April 15-16 (Folder 11)
      - Pavia, 1941 (Folder 12)
  - Finnish Martta Work. Photo reproductions (Folder 13)
  - Food
    - General. Includes Food Program (Folder 14-15)
    - Agricultural production for Finland
      - General (Box 186, Folder 1)
      - Raisins for Finland (Folder 2)
      - Seeds for Finland (Folder 3)
  - Furniture and equipment (Folder 4)
  - Gifts
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Foodstuffs (Folder 6)
    - Medical supplies (Folder 7)
    - Painting (Folder 8)
    - Sugar (Folder 9)
    - Wheat (Folder 10)
  - Girl scouts. Letters of American girl scouts to girl scouts of Finland (Folder 11)
  - Granges (Folder 12)
  - Hospitals
    - General (Folder 13)
    - Children's hospitals in Finland (Folder 14)
  - Industrial equipment (Folder 15)
  - Lutheran church (Folder 16)
  - Medical supplies, purchased for Finland
    - General
      - General (Folder 17)
      - 1940 (Folder 18)
      - 1941
        - January-April (Folder 19)
        - May-December (Folder 20)
    - Penicillin (Folder 21)
  - Mennonite Brethren Church of North America (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - New York World's Fair, (Finnish Pavilion), 1940 (Folder 2)
  - Oil (Folder 3)
  - Orphanages (Folder 4)
  - Refugees - Children (Folder 5)
  - Shipping and shippers (Folder 6)
  - Textiles (Folder 7)
  - Wihuri Research Institute, Helsinki (Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 9)
- American Scandinavian Division File, 1939-1940
  Acknowledgements, appeals for support, bank deposits, correspondence, lists, maps, memoranda, press releases, publicity material, receipt books, reports, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - Correspondence (Box 188)
    - General
      - General
        - General (Folder 1)
        - Danish Division (Folder 2)
        - Finnish Division (Folder 3)
        - Norwegian Division (Folder 4)
        - Swedish Division (Folder 5)
      - Ekelund, L. D. (Folder 6-8)
      - Lindbergh, Otto (Folder 9)
    - State chairmen. Includes list of state chairmen
      - General (Folder 10)
      - California (Folder 11)
      - Connecticut (Folder 12)
      - Indiana (Folder 13)
      - Iowa (Folder 14)
      - Kansas (Folder 15)
      - Louisiana (Folder 16)
      - Maryland (Folder 17)
      - Minnesota (Folder 18)
      - Montana (Folder 19)
      - New York (Box 189)
        - Brooklyn (Folder 1)
        - Buffalo (Folder 2)
        - White Plains (Folder 3)
      - North Dakota (Folder 4)
      - Oregon (Folder 5)
      - Pennsylvania (Folder 6)
      - South Dakota (Folder 7)
      - West Virginia (Folder 8)
  - Fundraising file
    - General (Folder 9)
    - Acknowledgments of donations received
      - General
        - General (Folder 10-14)
        - Business establishments (Folder 15)
        - Newspapers (Folder 16)
      - Sawtelle, Raymond (Box 190, Folder 1-2)
    - Appeals for support
      - General
        - General (Folder 3)
        - Saarinen, Eliel (Folder 4)
      - Academic institutions (Folder 5)
      - Business establishments (Folder 6-8)
      - Churches
        - General (Folder 9)
        - Finnish (Folder 10)
        - Swedish (Folder 11)
      - National organizations - Sweden (Box 191)
        - Business (Folder 1-2)
        - Newspapers (Folder 3)
        - Social (Folder 4-7)
      - Professional and social organizations
        - General (Folder 8-11)
        - Bygdelagenes Faellesraad (Box 192, Folder 1)
        - Daughters of Norway (Folder 2)
        - Entertainers (Folder 3)
        - Singing societies (Norwegian) (Folder 4)
        - Ski clubs and winter sport societies (Folder 5)
        - Sons of Norway (Folder 6)
    - Bank deposits
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Alaska-Michigan (Folder 8-26)
      - Minnesota-New Jersay (Box 193, Folder 1-8)
      - New York
        - General (Folder 9)
        - New York City
          - General (Folder 10)
          - Chase National Bank (Folder 11-13)
          - Chase National Bank (Box 194, Folder 1-3)
          - Federal Reserve Bank of New York (Folder 4)
          - Irving Trust Company (Folder 5)
          - National City Bank of New York (Folder 6)
          - Union National Bank (Folder 7)
      - North Carolina-Wisconsin (Folder 8-14)
      - North Carolina-Wisconsin (Box 195, Folder 1-6)
    - Lists
      - Churches and social organizations (Folder 7-8)
      - Individuals and organizations with Scandinavian connections (Folder 9-10)
    - Maps of Finland (for sale) (Folder 11)
    - Memoranda, Inter-office (Folder 12)
    - Press relations file
      - Clippings (Folder 13)
      - Correspondence with editors (Folder 14)
      - Press releases (Folder 15)
    - Publicity file
      - General (Folder 16)
      - Lists of Scandinavian newspapers in the U.S. (Folder 17)
      - Programs of events
    - Questionnaires (Box 196, Folder 1-8)
    - Questionnaires (Box 197, Folder 1-6)
    - Receipt books (Folder 7)
    - Reports (Box 198)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Structure and organization of the American Scandinavian Division (Folder 2)
    - Subject file
      - Coin boxes (Folder 3)
      - Lecture Bureau
        - General (Folder 4)
        - Correspondence with Birger Nordholm (Folder 5-9)
        - Correspondence with Birger Nordholm (Box 199, Folder 1-7)
        - Correspondence with Birger Nordholm (Box 200, Folder 1-3)
        - Lists of speakers (Folder 4)
        - Speeches and radio talks (Folder 5)
        - Telegrams (Folder 6)
      - Scandinavian volunteer workers, 1939-1940 (Folder 7)
      - Sponsorship drive (Folder 8)
- Industrial Division File, 1939-1940
  Acknowledgements, correspondence, form letters, lists, memoranda, personnel records, press releases, requests relating mostly to activities of industries and businesses, arranged alphabetically by subject
  - Acknowledgments (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - General (Folder 2)
      - A-I (Folder 3)
      - J-P (Folder 4)
      - R-Z (Folder 5)
    - Gehle, Frederick (Folder 6-9)
    - Hoover, Herbert (Folder 10)
  - Employee solicitations (Folder 11)
  - Form letters (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising file - Luncheons (Folder 2)
  - Organization and operations file (Folder 3)
  - Lists
    - Donations (Folder 4)
    - Industrial chairmen (Folder 5)
  - Memoranda (Folder 6)
  - Personnel file (Folder 7)
  - Press releases. Includes clippings (Folder 8)
  - Requests to serve as chairmen (Folder 9)
  - Requests to serve as chairmen (Box 203, Folder 1-2)
  - Subject file
    - Business employees (Folder 3)
    - Coin boxes (Folder 4)
    - Industries and businesses
      - General (Folder 5)
      - Advertisement (Folder 6)
      - Automobile and motor companies (Folder 7)
      - Automotive (Folder 8)
      - Aviation (Folder 9)
      - Banking (Folder 10-11)
      - Boots and shoes (Box 204, Folder 1)
      - Bottling (Folder 2)
      - Breweries (Folder 3)
      - Building (Folder 4)
      - Can manufacturers and canneries (Folder 5)
      - Carbonated beverages (Folder 6)
      - Chain stores (Folder 7)
      - Chemical manufacturers (Folder 8)
      - Civil Service (Folder 9)
      - Clothing (Folder 10-11)
      - Coal producers (Box 205, Folder 1-2)
      - Communication groups (Folder 3)
      - Confectionery (Folder 4)
      - Construction (Folder 5)
      - Cutlery (Folder 6)
      - Dairy (Folder 7)
      - Department stores (Folder 8)
      - Drugs and cosmetics (Folder 9-10)
      - Electrical companies (Box 206, Folder 1)
      - Exchanges
        - General (Folder 2)
        - Coffee, sugar, cocoa (Folder 3)
        - Produce (Folder 4)
        - Stock, New York (Folder 5)
      - Floor covering (Folder 6)
      - Flour (Folder 7)
      - Furniture (Folder 8)
      - Graphic arts (Folder 9)
      - Hides and leather (Folder 10)
      - Hotels (Folder 11)
      - Industrial machinery (Folder 12)
      - Industrial machinery (Box 207, Folder 1-2)
      - Insurance
        - General (Folder 3-5)
        - Brokers (Folder 6)
        - Casualty, surety (Folder 7)
        - Fire and marine (Folder 8)
        - Mutual life (Folder 9)
      - Jewelry (Folder 10)
      - Knitting yarn and wool (Folder 11)
      - Launderers and dyers (Box 208, Folder 1)
      - Liquor
        - Distillers (Folder 2)
        - Importers (Folder 3)
        - Rectifiers (Folder 4)
        - Retailers (Folder 5)
        - Wholesalers (Folder 6)
        - Wine (Folder 7)
      - Lithograph (Folder 8)
      - Lumber (Folder 9)
      - Manufacture (Folder 10)
      - Marine industries
        - General (Folder 11)
        - Drafsmen (Folder 12)
        - Steamships (Folder 13)
      - Meat processors (Folder 14)
      - Metals (Folder 15)
      - Mining and smelting (Folder 16)
      - Office equipment (Folder 17)
      - Paints and varnishes (Box 209, Folder 1)
      - Paper (Folder 2-3)
      - Petroleum (Folder 4)
      - Photographic equipment (Folder 5)
      - Printing (Folder 6)
      - Publishing (Folder 7)
      - Railroads (Folder 8-10)
      - Real estate (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - Restaurants (Folder 2)
      - Rubber (Folder 3)
      - Savings banks
        - General (Folder 4)
        - New York-New Jersey (Folder 5)
      - Soap (Folder 6)
      - Steel (Folder 7)
      - Sugar (Folder 8)
      - Telephone companies (Folder 9)
      - Textiles (Box 211, Folder 1)
      - Tobacco (Folder 2)
      - Travel bureaus (Folder 3)
      - Utilities (Folder 4)
    - Professions
      - Accounting (Folder 5-6)
      - Advertising (Folder 7)
      - Law (Folder 8)
    - Volunteers (Folder 9)
- Labor Division File, 1940
  Acknowledgements, articles, cards, correspondence, form letters, lists, memoranda, pamphlets, receipts, reports, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - General. Includes material re organization of division (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Articles
    - General (Folder 2)
    - By A. S. Lipton published in Justice on fight to preserve freedom (Folder 3)
  - Cards (Folder 4)
  - Contributions
    - Foreign (Folder 5)
    - National (arranged alphabetically by state)
      - A-C (Folder 6)
      - D-G (Folder 7)
      - I (Folder 8)
      - I (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - K (Folder 2)
      - M (Folder 3)
      - N
        - General (Folder 4)
        - New York (Folder 5)
      - O (Folder 6)
      - P (Folder 7)
      - R-V (Folder 8)
      - W (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence
    - General (Folder 2)
    - Edwards, H. M. (Folder 3)
    - Foreign labor organizations (Folder 4)
    - Green, William (Folder 5)
    - Lipsett, Alexander
      - General (Folder 6)
      - Cablegrams (Folder 7)
    - Woll, Matthew (Folder 8)
  - Form letters (Folder 9-10)
  - Lists (Box 215)
    - Local unions (Folder 1)
    - State representatives (Folder 2)
  - Memoranda (Folder 3)
  - Pamphlets (Folder 4)
  - Receipts (Folder 5)
  - Reports, speeches, and statements
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Lipsett, Alexander (Folder 7)
  - Subject file
    - Dutch Treat Luncheon at Commodore Hotel (Folder 8)
    - Finnish Labor Day (Folder 9)
- Motion Picture Division File, 1940
  Correspondence, financial statements, form letters, lists of theaters, memoranda, press releases, reports, statements, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - Correspondence (Box 216)
    - General (Folder 1)
    - Clippings (Folder 2)
    - Censor boards (Folder 3)
    - Connolly, Jack (Folder 4)
    - Hart, Vincent, director of division
      - A (Folder 5)
      - B (Folder 6)
      - C (Folder 7)
      - D-G (Folder 8)
      - H-J (Folder 9)
      - K-M (Folder 10)
      - O-S (Folder 11)
    - T-Z (Folder 12)
    - Mecca Laboratories (Folder 13)
    - Theater owners (Box 217)
      - B-H (Folder 1)
      - L-M (Folder 2)
    - N-Z (Folder 3)
    - Thompson, L. (Folder 4)
    - Yorke, Emerson (Folder 5)
  - Financial statements (Folder 6)
  - Form letters (Folder 7)
  - Lists of theaters
    - A-L (Folder 8)
    - M-O (Folder 9)
    - P-Z (Folder 10)
  - Memoranda (Box 218)
    - General (Folder 1)
    - Hopkins, John (Folder 2)
  - Press releases (Folder 3)
  - Radio releases (Folder 4)
  - Reports
    - Attendance at film viewings (Folder 5)
    - Contributions (Folder 6)
  - Statements (Folder 7)
  - Subject file - Finland Fights
    - Correspondence
      - General (Folder 8-10)
      - State chairmen
        - Alabama (Folder 11)
        - Arizona (Folder 12)
        - Arkansas (Folder 13)
        - California (Folder 14)
        - Colorado (Folder 15)
        - Connecticut (Folder 16)
        - District of Columbia (Folder 17)
        - Florida (Folder 18)
        - Georgia (Folder 19)
        - Illinois (Folder 20)
        - Indiana (Folder 21)
        - Iowa (Folder 22)
        - Kansas (Folder 23)
        - Kentucky (Folder 24)
        - Louisiana (Folder 25)
        - Maine (Folder 26)
        - Maryland (Folder 27)
        - Massachusetts (Folder 28)
        - Michigan (Folder 29)
        - Minnesota (Box 219, Folder 1)
        - Mississippi (Folder 2)
        - Missouri (Folder 3)
        - Montana (Folder 4)
        - Nebraska (Folder 5)
        - Nevada (Folder 6)
        - New Hampshire (Folder 7)
        - New Jersey (Folder 8)
        - New Mexico (Folder 9)
        - New York (Folder 10)
        - North Carolina (Folder 11)
        - North Dakota (Folder 12)
        - Ohio (Folder 13)
        - Oklahoma (Folder 14)
        - Oregon (Folder 15)
        - Pennsylvania (Folder 16)
        - Rhode Island (Folder 17)
        - South Carolina (Folder 18)
        - Tennessee (Folder 19)
        - Texas (Folder 20)
        - Utah (Folder 21)
        - Vermont (Folder 22)
        - Virginia (Folder 23)